

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Recent graduate in computer science with strong mathematical skills and software engineering emphasis, interested in everything from AI to fullstack development. Previous experience includes a deep background in humanities and languages with international teaching experience.

SKILLS

- Software Engineering
- Fullstack Engineering
- Mathematics

- Natural Languages
- Project Management
- Al/ML

- Audio Engineering
- Databases

EXPERIENCE

Graduate Student Teaching Assistant

March 2020 - June 2020

- Portland State University | Portand, OR
 Helped students with coursework in Frontend Web Technologies course.
- Graded assignments for Discrete Math course.

Teacher May 2010 - August 2016

Various

- Summer 2016: Taught ESL to high school students from Spain.
- 9/15-6/16: Taught Chinese and second grade using Connections Academy.
- Spring 2015: Taught ESL to various ages in Itoshima, Japan
- Fall/Winter 2014: Taught ESL to various ages in Chongqing, China
- 5/10-6/11: Taught ESL to kindergarten kids in Beijing, China.

Teahouse Personnel

October 2007 - June 2018

Brew Dr. Tea | Portland, OR

• Various roles: barista, delivery driver, warehouse management.

EDUCATION

Master's Computer Science (3.95 GPA)

June 2020

Portland State University, Portland, OR

Accelerated Undergraduate Computer Science

2019

Portland State University, Portland, OR

Audio Engineering 2018

Portland Community College, Portland, OR

Post-Bacc Inquiry: World History, Politics, Economics, German, etc. Portland State University, Portland, OR	2015
Mandarin Chinese HSK 5 and Advanced Oral HSK	2014
Confucius Institute, Portland, OR	2014
Bachelor of Arts English Literature	2009
Portland State University, Portland, OR	

LANGUAGES

English, Chinese, Spanish

PROGRAMMING

C, C++, Java, Android, Python, Javascript, React, Haskell, SQL

PROJECTS

Portfolio: https://charboltron.github.io

LINKS

Github: https://www.github/charboltron

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/charboltron/ Fullstack App: https://best-trivia-game.herokuapp.com/